Guide to the Arabic Film Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Arabic film poster collection
1935-2005
MS 1868
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
33
The collection is comprised of 1284 film posters, 156 film lobby cards, and 96 film press books from Arab countries. The majority of the items are from Egypt, but include pieces from Algeria, Iraq, Lebanon, Syria and other countries.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from al-Furat Publishing and Distribution Company, Beirut, Lebanon, and transferred to Manuscripts and Archives by the curator of the Near Eastern Collection, 2006.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Arrangement
Arranged in five series: I. Posters, 1935-2005. II. Lobby Cards, 1948-1993. III. Press Books, 1954-1989. IV. Half Sheets, 1949-1974. V. Fragile Posters - Egypt, 1956-1961.
Scope and Contents
The collection is comprised of 1284 film posters, 156 film lobby cards, and 96 film press books from Arab countries. The majority of the items are from Egypt, but include pieces from Algeria, Iraq, Lebanon, Syria and other countries.
Film posters; Lobby cards; Pressbooks (theatre manuals)
- Posters, 1935-2005; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  The series is arranged alphabetically by country. When viewing, researchers should maintain the established order of the posters within each box.
  - Algeria:ma'rakit al-jaza'ir, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Egypt
    - Ana wahdi, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Ayyam bila hub, undated (Box 1)
    - Gharamiat majnun, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Fursan akhir zaman, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Faris al-madinah, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Ful al-ful, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Ful al-sin al-'azim, 2004 (Box 1)
    - Firqit banat wa bas, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Fatah min isra'il, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Futuwat al-nas al-ghalabah, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Fi baytina rajul, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Viva zalata, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Fakh al-jawasis, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Faris bani hamdan, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Fuqara' wa lakin su'ada', 1984 (Box 1)
    - Fata ahlami, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Futuwat al-jabal, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Kulh tamam, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Kan wa kan wa kan, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Qisat al-hay al-gharbi, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Qadam al-khayr, 1952 (Box 2)
    - Qahir al-zalam, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Qahwit al-mawardi, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Qamar al-zaman, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Qalb al-layl, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Qahir al-zaman, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Qa' al-madinah, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Qafas al-harim, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Qamar al-layl, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Qasir fi al-hawa', undated (Box 2)
    - Fi al-sayf lazim nihib, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Fituwat bulaq, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Liman tashruq al-shams, 1977 (Box 3)
    - La tatrukni wahdi, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Kimu wa antimu, undated (Box 3)
    - Kayd al-'awalim, undated (Box 3)
    - Kart ahmar, 1994 (Box 3)
    - Ka's al-'adhab, 1952 (Box 3)
    - Karim ibn al-shaykh, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Kuluhum fi al-nar, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Kalimit sharaf, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Kayfa tatakhallas min zawjatik, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Kayduhum 'azim, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Kunuz, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Kaburyah, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Kul hadha al-hub, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Karakun fi al-shari', 1986 (Box 3)
    - Lahin al-sa'adah, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Liqa' ma' al-madi, 1975 (Box 4)
    - Layl wa raghbah, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Layali yasmin, 1978 (Box 4)
    - La... ya man kunta habibi, 1976 (Box 4)
    - La tabki... ya habiba al-'umir, 1979 (Box 4)
    - Lahin al-khulud, 1952 (Box 4)
    - Laylit shita' dafi'ah, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Layh ya banafsij, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Lu'bit kul yawm, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Layh ya dunya, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Lastu mustahtirah, 1971 (Box 4)
    - La... ya umi, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Lahib al-intiqam, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Laylah sakhinah, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Mau'id gharam, 1956 (Box 5)
    - Mabka al-'ushshaq, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Mudaris khususi, 1965 (Box 5)
    - La'nit imra'ah, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Laylit al-dukhlah, 1950 (Box 5)
    - Lan a'ud, 1959 (Box 5)
    - La anam, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Lu'bit al-hub wa al-jawaz, 1964 (Box 5)
    - La tutfi' al-shams, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Laylit al-qabid 'ala fatimah, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Laylah baka fiha al-qamar, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Laylit al-zafaf, 1966 (Box 5)
    - La waqta lil dumu', 1975 (Box 5)
    - Lughit al-hub, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Lahazat khawf, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Mursi fawq mursi that, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Jazirat al-'arab, undated (Box 6)
    - Mau'id ma'a al-habib, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Muhimah fi tal abib, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Mujrim ma'a martabit al-sharaf, undated (Box 6)
    - Mal wa nisa', 1960 (Box 6)
    - Mau'id ma'a al-ra'is, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Madrasit al-mushaghibin, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Muwatin wa mukhbir wa harami, undated (Box 6)
    - Mudhakarat murahiqah, undated (Box 6)
    - Muhami khul', 2002 (Box 6)
    - Min nazrit 'ayn, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Majanin bi al-wirathah, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Munyat shababi, undated (Box 6)
    - Min ghayr mi'ad, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Malak wa shaytan, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Muluk al-dahik, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Min ajli al-hayah, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Min al-bayt lilmadrasah, undated (Box 7)
    - Mamnu' al-hub, 1942 (Box 7)
    - Mukhaymir.. da'iman jahiz, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Madrasit al-murahiqin, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Min ajil imra'ah, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Mau'id ma'a al majhul, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Ma ba'da al-hub, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Musajil khatar, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Mulid ya dunya, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Mudhakarat tilmidhah, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Min yijanin min ?, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Makhalib imra'ah, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Sanawat al-hub, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Sukar hanim, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Ma 'aqdarsh, 1946 (Box 8)
    - Miramar, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Min yiqdar 'ala 'azizah, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Marzuqah, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Milyun jinayh, 1953 (Box 8)
    - Mujrim fi ijazah, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Min ajil hanafi, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Mutaham.. rughma anfih, undated (Box 8)
    - Mau'id ma'a al-qadar, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Muhimah sa'bah jidan, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Muhami tahta al-tamrin, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Ma' hubi... wa ashwaqi, 1977 (Box 8)
    - Mughamirun hawla al-'alam, 1979 (Box 8)
    - Samra' sina', 1959 (Box 9)
    - Sijin al-'adhara, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Suq al-silah, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Sukut ha nisawar, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Sijin bila qudban, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Siqan fi al-wahil, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Sa'aktub ismak 'ala al-rimal, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Sir al-gha'ib, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Sir imra'ah, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Su'al fi al-hub, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Supir markit, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Sultan, 1958 (Box 9)
    - Sikit safar, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Sama' hus, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Um kalthum, undated (Box 9)
    - Saffah al-nisa', 1970 (Box 10)
    - Sunya wa al-majnun, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Sayyid al-'atifi, 2005 (Box 10)
    - Sallim 'ala al-habayib, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Salasil min harir, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Sultanit al-sahra', 1947 (Box 10)
    - Salamah fi khayr, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Samarah al-amir, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Sayyidati anisati, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Sanah ula nasb, 2003 (Box 10)
    - Suq al mut'ah, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Sa'a'ud bila dumu', 1979 (Box 10)
    - Salam ya sahbi, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Suq al-nisa', 1994 (Box 10)
    - Sariq al-mihfazah, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Shurt wa fanilah wa kab, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Shibr wa nus, undated (Box 11)
    - Shawadir, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Shawish nis al-layl, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Shilni wa ashilak, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Shayatin al-layl, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Shabab fi 'asifah, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Shillayt al-murahiqin, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Shabab yarqus fawqa al-nar [two posters], 1978 (Box 11)
    - Shayatin al-bahir, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Sha'ban tahta al-sifir, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Shawq, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Shabab majnun jidan, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Shaqawit banat, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Shabab yahtariq, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Fi baytina rajul, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Thawrit al-madinah, undated (Box 12)
    - Amal, undated (Box 12)
    - Sahib sahbuh, 2002 (Box 12)
    - Sahy' mina al-'adhab, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Shahir 'asal basal, 1960 (Box 12)
    - Shati' al-gharam, 1950 (Box 12)
    - Shahirah, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Shams al-zinati, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Shayatin ila al-abad, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Shati' al-masatil, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Shay' mina al-hub, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Shati' al-'unf, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Shabab wa hub wa marah, 1964 (Box 12)
    - Shawari' min nar, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Sahyatin al-shurtah, 1990 (Box 12)
    - Shay' mina al-khawf, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Shabakit al-maut, 1990 (Box 12)
    - Sira' al-muhtarifin, 1969 (Box 13)
    - Sa'aydi fi al-jaysh, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Samt al-khirfan, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Sahib al-jalalah, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Sira' al-ahfad, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Sadiqi al-wafi, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Sarkhit nadam, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Safqah ma'a imra'ah, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Sa'id al-nisa', 1975 (Box 13)
    - Sira' al-'ushaq, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Sibyan wa banat, 1965 (Box 13)
    - Suwar mamnu'ah, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Sabrin, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Sa'aydi fi al-jami'ah al-amrikiah, 1998 (Box 13)
    - Sira' al-zawjat, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 'Aylit zizi, 1963 (Box 14)
    - 'Indama yughani al-hub, 1973 (Box 14)
    - 'Ala bab al-wazir, 1981 (Box 14)
    - 'Antar shayil sayfuh, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Tarid al-firdaws, 1965 (Box 14)
    - Tariq al-shuk, 1950 (Box 14)
    - Tariq al-dumu', 1961 (Box 14)
    - Tuyur al-zalam, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Ta'ir al-layl al-hazin, 1977 (Box 14)
    - Tariq al-shaytan, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Darbit shamis, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Darbit mu'alim, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Da' al-'umir ya waladi, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Did al-hukumah, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Dihk wa li'b wa jad wa hub, 1993 (Box 14)
    - 'Ish al-gharam, 1959 (Box 15)
    - 'Ala difaf al-nil, 1963 (Box 15)
    - 'Ashur kalb al-asad, 1961 (Box 15)
    - 'Asifah min al-dumu', 1979 (Box 15)
    - 'Alam mudhik jidan, 1968 (Box 15)
    - 'Amal ayh al-hub fi baba... !, 1980 (Box 15)
    - 'Uthman al-jabar, 1968 (Box 15)
    - 'Awiz yihib, undated (Box 15)
    - 'Adhra' wa lakin, 1977 (Box 15)
    - 'Antar wa 'ablah, 1945 (Box 15)
    - 'Adu al-mar'ah, 1966 (Box 15)
    - 'Aris bint al-wazir, 1970 (Box 15)
    - 'Indama yasqut al-jasad, 1977 (Box 15)
    - 'Adhra' al-basrah, 1962 (Box 15)
    - 'Adawiyah, 1968 (Box 15)
    - 'Anbar al-mawt, 1988 (Box 16)
    - 'Atabit al-sitat, 1995 (Box 16)
    - 'Umar 2000 (Box 16)
    - 'Abud 'ala al-hudud, 1999 (Box 16)
    - 'Afwan ayuha al-qanun, undated (Box 16)
    - 'Arusah wa jawz 'irsan, 1982 (Box 16)
    - 'Awdit al-ibn al-dal, 1976 (Box 16)
    - 'Ukal, 2004 (Box 16)
    - 'Ashiq al-ruh, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 'Asir al-quwah, undated (Box 16)
    - 'Ayb ya lulu... ya lulu 'ayb, 1978 (Box 16)
    - 'Ashat lil hub, 1959 (Box 16)
    - 'Awatif, 1958 (Box 16)
    - 'Isabit hamadah wa tutu, 1982 (Box 16)
    - 'A'ilat muhtaramah, 1969 (Box 16)
    - 'Ala kayfak, undated (Box 17)
    - Nahid, undated (Box 17)
    - Ghawi mashakil, 1980 (Box 17)
    - Gharam tilmidhah, 1972 (Box 17)
    - Ghaltit habibi, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Ghaltit um, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Ghazil al-banat, 1949 (Box 17)
    - Ghabi minuh fih, 2004 (Box 17)
    - 'Askar fi al-mu'askar, undated (Box 17)
    - 'Ifritu, 1999 (Box 17)
    - 'Indama nuhib, 1967 (Box 17)
    - 'Awdit madrasit al-mushaghibin, 2001 (Box 17)
    - 'Alam 'iyal... 'iyal, undated (Box 17)
    - 'Antar ibn shaddad, 1960 (Box 17)
    - 'Ifritah hanim, 1949 (Box 17)
    - 'Ifrit al-nahar, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Halit hub, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Harib al-farawlah, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Hub al-banat, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Halit murahaqah, 1989 (Box 18)
    - Habibi... da'iman, 1980 (Box 18)
    - Hayati 'adhab, 1979 (Box 18)
    - Harit burjuwan, 1989 (Box 18)
    - Hakamit al-mahkamah, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Gharamiyat imra'ah, 1960 (Box 18)
    - Ghadan yawm akhar, 1961 (Box 18)
    - Gharibah, 1963 (Box 18)
    - Ghadan sa'antaqim, 1982 (Box 18)
    - Ghadab al-halim, 1984 (Box 18)
    - Gharib... fi bayti, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Gharam fi al-tariq al-zira'i, 1971 (Box 18)
    - Shabab al-yawm, undated (Box 19)
    - 'Ahid al-hawa, undated (Box 19)
    - Khitat sl-shaytan, 1988 (Box 19)
    - Khatib mama..., 1971 (Box 19)
    - Khiyanah, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Khataya al-hub, 1976 (Box 19)
    - Khatafu al-banat, undated (Box 19)
    - Khali balak min zuzu, 1972 (Box 19)
    - Kha'ifah... min shay' ma, 1978 (Box 19)
    - Khalid ibn al-walid, 1958 (Box 19)
    - Khali...balak min 'aqlak, 1984 (Box 19)
    - Hubbak nar, 2004 (Box 19)
    - Habib al-'umir, 1947 (Box 19)
    - Hub fawqa al-burkan, undated (Box 19)
    - Hubi al-wahid, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Halal 'alayk, 1952 (Box 19)
    - Haramiah x ki ji 2, 2002 (Box 19)
    - Du'a' al-karawan, 1959 (Box 20)
    - Darb al-jid'an, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Dalal al-masriyah, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Da'una nuhib, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Da'uni antaqim, 1979 (Box 20)
    - Dima' 'ala al-nil, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Khabtit al-'umir, 1990 (Box 20)
    - Khalik ma'a allah, 1954 (Box 20)
    - Khulud, 1948 (Box 20)
    - Khamsah fi al-jahim, 1981 (Box 20)
    - Khalati faransa, 2004 (Box 20)
    - 85 jinayat, undated (Box 20)
    - Khamsah bab, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Khali balak min jiranak, 1979 (Box 20)
    - Kharaja wa lam ya'ud, 1984 (Box 20)
    - Dala' al-banat, 1969 (Box 21)
    - Darb al-hawa, 1983 (Box 21)
    - Da'wah lil hayah, 1973 (Box 21)
    - Dik al-barabir, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Disku disku, 1994 (Box 21)
    - Dima' 'ala al-isfalt, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Dunya 'abd al-jabar, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Darb al-libanah, 1984 (Box 21)
    - Dumu' sahibat al-jalalah, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Dumu' al-hub, 1935 (Box 21)
    - Dima' 'ala al-thawb al-wardi, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Dindush, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Dumu' fi laylit al-zafaf, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Diluni ya nas, 1954 (Box 21)
    - Da'ni wa al-dumu', 1964 (Box 21)
    - Raghabat mamnu'ah, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Rihlah ladhidhah, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Risalah min imra'ah majhulah, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Rajul wa imra'atan, 1966 (Box 22)
    - Rasif nimrah 5, 1956 (Box 22)
    - Rihlat al-'aja'ib, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Rud al-faraj, 1987 (Box 22)
    - Rajul bim'na al-kalimah, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Rawyah, 1946 (Box 22)
    - Rabhah, 1943 (Box 22)
    - Rabi'a al-'adawiyah, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Dhat al-wajhayn, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Dhikrayat tilmidhah, 1965 (Box 22)
    - Dantila, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Dima' fi al-sahra', 1950 (Box 22)
    - Zaman ya hub, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Rajul faqada 'aqluh, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Rihlit hub, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Rihlit al-nisyan, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Raya wa sakinah, 1953 (Box 23)
    - Raya wa sakinah, undated (Box 23)
    - Rihlit shahir al-'asal, 1970 (Box 23)
    - Rajab fawqa safih sakhin, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Rajul fi wartah, 1994 (Box 23)
    - Risalah ila al-wali, 1998 (Box 23)
    - Rumantika, 1996 (Box 23)
    - Rida bund, 1970 (Box 23)
    - Raghbah mutawahisha, 1991 (Box 23)
    - Rajul fi sijin al-nisa', 1982 (Box 23)
    - Rijal la ya'rifun al-hub, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Infijar, undated (Box 24)
    - Inhiyar, 1981 (Box 24)
    - Inahum yasruqun al-aranib, 1983 (Box 24)
    - Ana al-harib, 1962 (Box 24)
    - Ana hurah, 1959 (Box 24)
    - Zaki shan, 2004 (Box 24)
    - Zawj bil ijar, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Zaman hatim zahran, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Zuhur bariyyah, 1973 (Box 24)
    - Zizit, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Zawjah min al-shari', 1960 (Box 24)
    - Zawj tahta al-talab, 1985 (Box 24)
    - Zawjah muharramah, 1991 (Box 24)
    - Za'ir al-fajir, 1974 (Box 24)
    - Zawjah min baris, 1966 (Box 24)
    - Ana wa huwa wa hiya, 1964 (Box 25)
    - Ana wa banati, 1961 (Box 25)
    - Indhar bi al-ta'ah, 1993 (Box 25)
    - Ana wa al-'adhab wa hawak, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Inahu qadari, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Anisat wa syyidat, 1974 (Box 25)
    - Ini uttaham, 1960 (Box 25)
    - Ana... la 'aqilah wa la majnunah, 1976 (Box 25)
    - Intakhibu al-duktur sulaiman'abd al-basit, 1981 (Box 25)
    - Ana mish haramiyah, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Anta habibi, 1957 (Box 25)
    - Ana al-majnun, 1981 (Box 25)
    - Intabihu ayuha al-sadah, 1980 (Box 25)
    - Ana ili qatalt al-hanash, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Ana fi 'aynayih, 1981 (Box 25)
    - Ahil al-qimah, undated (Box 26)
    - Ayamuna al-hilawah, undated (Box 26)
    - Ayna al-mafar?, 1977 (Box 26)
    - Ayna 'aqli, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Ayam al-tahadi, 1985 (Box 26)
    - Ayam al-'umir ma'dudah, 1978 (Box 26)
    - Ays krim fi jlim, 1992 (Box 26)
    - Ayub, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Ayam al-sadat, 2001 (Box 26)
    - Ayam wa layali [two posters], 1955 (Box 26)
    - Ay ay, 1992 (Box 26)
    - Ah... wa ah min sharbat, 1992 (Box 26)
    - Ah ya layl ya zaman, 1976 (Box 26)
    - Ah min hawwa', 1962 (Box 26)
    - Ana wahdi, 1952 (Box 26)
    - Imra'ah ayilah lilsuqut, 1991 (Box 27)
    - Al-wad sayyid al-shaghal, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Aqwa al-rijal, undated (Box 27)
    - Al-banat wa al-marsidis, 1972 (Box 27)
    - Al-ghadab, 1972 (Box 27)
    - Al-siyasi, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Al-limbi, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Illi bali balak, undated (Box 27)
    - Al-lu'bah, 1977 (Box 27)
    - Al-tha'alib, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Al-nadhdharah al-sawda', 1963 (Box 27)
    - Ula thanawi, undated (Box 27)
    - Alf laylah wa laylah, undated (Box 27)
    - Alf busah wa busah, undated (Box 27)
    - Al-usta hasan, 1952 (Box 27)
    - Bul bul afandi, 1948 (Box 28)
    - Batal lilnihayah, 1963 (Box 28)
    - Bahbuh afandi, 1958 (Box 28)
    - Bambah kashshar, 1974 (Box 28)
    - Budhur al-shaytan, 1978 (Box 28)
    - Bakhit wa 'adilah 2, 1997 (Box 28)
    - Bariq 'aynayki, 1982 (Box 28)
    - Budur, 1974 (Box 28)
    - Bahiyyah, 1960 (Box 28)
    - Bur sa'id, 1957 (Box 28)
    - Bint badi'ah, 1972 (Box 28)
    - Bus shuf sukkar biti'mil ayh !, 1975 (Box 28)
    - Baqaya 'adhra', 1962 (Box 28)
    - Banat fi al-jami'ah, 1971 (Box 28)
    - Iskandariyah niuyurk, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Tujjar al-mawt, 1957 (Box 29)
    - Bawabit iblis, 1993 (Box 29)
    - Bayna qalbayn, 1953 (Box 29)
    - Birlanti, 1944 (Box 29)
    - Burj al-'adhra', 1971 (Box 29)
    - Batal min waraq, 1988 (Box 29)
    - Bint wa ismuha mahmud ?, 1975 (Box 29)
    - Banatuna fi al-kharij, 1984 (Box 29)
    - Burkan al-ghadab, 2002 (Box 29)
    - Bilyah...wa dimaghuh al-'alyah, 2000 (Box 29)
    - Bahibak.. wa ana kaman, 2003 (Box 29)
    - Bint al-hitah, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Bayna al-atlal, 1959 (Box 29)
    - Bila 'awdah, 1961 (Box 29)
    - Bila dumu', 1961 (Box 29)
    - 3 Qisas, 1968 (Box 30)
    - Thalathah 'ala al-tariq, 1993 (Box 30)
    - 3 Rijal wa imra'ah, 1960 (Box 30)
    - Thuma tashruq al-shams, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Thalathah 'ala ma'idit al-dam, 1991 (Box 30)
    - 48 Sa'ah fi isra'il, 1998 (Box 30)
    - Thalathah 'ala wahid, 1990 (Box 30)
    - 3 Fatayat murahiqat, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Tasrih bi al-qatil, 1991 (Box 30)
    - Titu, 2004 (Box 30)
    - Tuut tuut, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Tazwir fi awraq rasmiyyah, 1984 (Box 30)
    - Tawhidah, 1976 (Box 30)
    - Tahadi al-aqwiya', 1980 (Box 30)
    - Tijibiha kidah tijibiha kidah... hiya kidah, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Jamal 'abd al-nasir, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Jahim 2, 1990 (Box 31)
    - Jabarut imra'ah, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Jawaz 'ala al-hawa, 1976 (Box 31)
    - Jawaz biqarar jumhuri, 2001 (Box 31)
    - Jarimat hub, 1959 (Box 31)
    - Jari al-wuhush, 1987 (Box 31)
    - Jawz mirati, 1961 (Box 31)
    - Jamilah al-jaza'iriyyah, 1958 (Box 31)
    - Jam'iyyaht qatil al-zawjat, 1962 (Box 31)
    - Junun al-hub, 1976 (Box 31)
    - Jarimah fi al-hay al-hadi, 1967 (Box 31)
    - Jaffat al-dumu', 1975 (Box 31)
    - Jahim al-ghirah, 1953 (Box 31)
    - Jins... na'im, 1975 (Box 31)
    - Hub ahla mina al-hub, 1975 (Box 32)
    - Hub fawqa al-sahab, 1983 (Box 32)
    - Hayat imra'ah, 1958 (Box 32)
    - Hikayati ma'a al-zaman, 1973 (Box 32)
    - Hayat wa amal, 1961 (Box 32)
    - Hammam al-malati, 1973 (Box 32)
    - Hafiyah 'ala jisir al-dhahab, 1976 (Box 32)
    - Hub wa kibriya', 1972 (Box 32)
    - Hub.. fi al-zinzanah, 1983 (Box 32)
    - Hikayit 3 banat, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Hikayit hub, 1959 (Box 32)
    - Jahim that al-ma', 1988 (Box 32)
    - Jawahir, 1949 (Box 32)
    - Jid'an bab al-shi'riyah, 1983 (Box 32)
    - Janab al-safir, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Hanafi al-ubbahah, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Hadith al-madinah, 1963 (Box 33)
    - Hawwa' wa al-qird, 1968 (Box 33)
    - Hubi... la yara al-shams, 1980 (Box 33)
    - Hub ila al-abad, 1959 (Box 33)
    - Hikayah fi kalimatayn, 1984 (Box 33)
    - Hikayit sha'b, 1957 (Box 33)
    - Hata naltaqi..., 1958 (Box 33)
    - Harami al-hub, 1976 (Box 33)
    - Hazimni ya, 1997 (Box 33)
    - Hayat ghaniyah, 1959 (Box 33)
    - Halit talabbus, 1987 (Box 33)
    - Hata akhir al-'umr, 1975 (Box 33)
    - Haram 'alayk, 1953 (Box 33)
    - Hilwah... ya dunya al-hub, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Al- fituwah, 1957 (Box 34)
    - Al-fadihah, 1992 (Box 34)
    - Al-ghul, 1983 (Box 34)
    - Al-'amaliqah, 1974 (Box 34)
    - Al-'aris yasil ghadan, 1963 (Box 34)
    - Al-'ashiqan, 2000 (Box 34)
    - Al-'askari shabrawi, 1962 (Box 34)
    - Al-'ar, 1982 (Box 34)
    - Al-'iyal al-tayibin, 1976 (Box 34)
    - Al-'abit, 1966 (Box 34)
    - Al-'alamayn, 1965 (Box 34)
    - Al-'atifah wa al-jasad, 1972 (Box 34)
    - Al-'a'ilah al-karimah, 1964 (Box 34)
    - Al-'adhra' wa al-sha'ir al-abyad, 1984 (Box 34)
    - Al-'aris al-thani, 1967 (Box 34)
    - Al-kaddab wa sahbuh, 1989 (Box 35)
    - Al-kammashah, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Al-kaddab, 1975 (Box 35)
    - Al-kaddabin al-talatah, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Al-karnak, 1975 (Box 35)
    - Al-kit kat, 1991 (Box 35)
    - Al-kafir, 1999 (Box 35)
    - Al-qalb wa ma yi'shaq, 1996 (Box 35)
    - Al-qahirah fi al-layl, 1963 (Box 35)
    - Al-qirish, 1981 (Box 35)
    - Al-qadi wa al-jallad, 1977 (Box 35)
    - Al-faris al-aswad, 1954 (Box 35)
    - Al-fanus al-sihri, 1960 (Box 35)
    - Al-firin, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Al-ghul sadiqi, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Al-mudir al-fani, 1965 (Box 36)
    - Allahu akbar, 1959 (Box 36)
    - Allahu ma'ana, 1955 (Box 36)
    - Al-la'nah, 1983 (Box 36)
    - Al-lis al-sharif, 1953 (Box 36)
    - Al-laylah al-akhirah, 1963 (Box 36)
    - Al-la'ib ma'a al-shayatin, 1991 (Box 36)
    - Al-li'qa' al-thani, 1967 (Box 36)
    - Al-lahib, 1964 (Box 36)
    - Al-la'ib ma'a al-kibar, 1991 (Box 36)
    - Al-lusus, 1981 (Box 36)
    - Al-la'ibah al-qadhirah, 1993 (Box 36)
    - Al-la'ib ma'a al-ashrar, 1993 (Box 36)
    - Al-layali al-dafi'ah, 1962 (Box 36)
    - Al-liqa' al-dami, 1992 (Box 36)
    - Al-murahiq al-kabir, 1961 (Box 37)
    - Al-mashbuh, 1980 (Box 37)
    - Al-mushaghib, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Al-mar'ah wa al-satur, 1997 (Box 37)
    - Al-mujrim, 1954 (Box 37)
    - Al-muwatin masri, 1991 (Box 37)
    - Al-mutasawwil, 1983 (Box 37)
    - Al-muntaqimun, 1984 (Box 37)
    - Al-mazaj, 1991 (Box 37)
    - Al-masatil, 1991 (Box 37)
    - Al-mushaghibat wa al-kabtin, 1991 (Box 37)
    - Al-mulid, 1989 (Box 37)
    - Al-muttahamah, 1942 (Box 37)
    - Al-mansi, 1993 (Box 37)
    - Al-majanin fi na'im, 1963 (Box 37)
    - Al-mar'ah wa al-qanun, undated (Box 38)
    - Al-mala'in, 1979 (Box 38)
    - Al-mudhnibun, 1976 (Box 38)
    - Al-haz wa 'abduh al-hamuli, undated (Box 38)
    - Al-muttahamah, 1990 (Box 38)
    - Al-mushaghibun fi al-jaysh, 1983 (Box 38)
    - Al-masir, 1997 (Box 38)
    - Al-majanin al-thalathah, 1970 (Box 38)
    - Al-mudmin, 1983 (Box 38)
    - Al-mihim al-hub, 1974 (Box 38)
    - Al-marid, 1964 (Box 38)
    - Al-ma'tuh, 1982 (Box 38)
    - Al-mu'alimah, 1958 (Box 38)
    - Al-mutamaridah, 1963 (Box 38)
    - Al-mustahil, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Al-wad mahrus bita' al wazir, 1999 (Box 39)
    - Al-harib, 1974 (Box 39)
    - Al-hanim bi al-niyabah 'an min?, 1987 (Box 39)
    - Al-hurub, 1991 (Box 39)
    - Al-hajjamah, 1992 (Box 39)
    - Al-halfut, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Al-namrud, 1956 (Box 39)
    - Al-nimir, 1952 (Box 39)
    - Al-nimir... wa al-untha, 1987 (Box 39)
    - Al-nawm fi al-'asal, 1996 (Box 39)
    - Al-nadam, 1978 (Box 39)